# Mengxi Nie

320 23rd Street South APT#528 Arlington, Virginia (202) 499-9388 niemengxi92@gmail.com

# **Summary**

I learn about computer science for more than 5 years and i am familiar with the knowledge of developing a software. Besides, I am good at Windows and Unix systems and commends. I am good at some programming language, such as C++, JAVA and so on. I have work experiences as a software tester and software developer.

#### Education

University of Electronic Science and Technology of China

September 2012 – June 2016

Bachelor

My major is information security, School of computer science and engineering.

#### The George Washington University

August 2016 – May 2018

Master, GPA 3.74

My major is computer science, School of engineering and applied science.

# **Employment History**

OUNAR.com

May 2015 – October 2015

Software Tester Internship

Beijing, China

I did some testing work there. I wrote testing cases and learnt about black-box testing, white-box testing, unit testing and so on.

#### **Global Tone Communication Technology Co. Ltd. (GTCOM)**

May 2017 – August 2017

Natural Language Processing Internship

Beijing, China

I learnt the basic NLP algorithm and wrote testing codes. Besides, as a sofeware developer, i wrote some projects in JAVA and Python and put them on-line. After debugging and testing using Tomcat, i released it.

### **Research & Publications**

## Science and Technology on Communication Security Laboratory, Chengdu, China

September 2014 – June 2016

#### **Conferences:**

- M. Nie, P. Ran and H. Yang, "Efficient Multi-keyword Ranked Search over Outsourced Cloud Data based on Homomorphic Encryption", MATEC Web of Conferences 56(2016), ICCAE 2016, DOI: 10.1051/matecconf/20165601002
- Y. Huang, H. Yang, M. Nie and H. Wu, "Image Feature Extraction with Homomorphic Encryption on Integer Vector", Proceeding ICMLSC 17 Proceedings of the 2017 International Conference on Machine Learning and Soft Computing, p.111-p.116, DOI: 10.1145/3036290.3036301

## **Professional Skills**

C++, JAVA, C: Expert Python, R, SQL: Advanced

Perl: Intermediate